

debora.yu@gmail.com 647-444-1212 debyucodes.com

github.com/debyucodes twitter.com/DebWebDev linkedin.com/in/deborayu

Skills

Coding Languages/Framworks:

HTML REACT CSS Firebase

JavaScript Git

JQuery AJAX / RESTful API

Additional skills:

Angular 2+ TypeScript Responsive Design WCAG Accessibility

Debora Yu

Front-End Developer

Profile

I am a Front-end developer, with strong analytical and communication skills. I like to combine my logical skills with creativity to build dynamic, accessible, responsive webpages and apps that provide excellent user experience. My past work experience allows me to develop strong instincts with the focus of meeting customer's needs.

Career Summary

Freelance Web
Developer

Self-employed

NOV 2019 - PRESENT

 Build dynamic websites with HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, ¡Query and React for small businesses

Maintain and debug products

Consult with clients to develop mock-ups, contents, designs

Laboratory Operation Supervisor

Torrance Compounding Pharmacy

MAY 2016 - JUNE 2020

- Supervise and train over 10 technicians, demonstrating strong leadership and communication skills
- Coordinate logistics and manage inventory with excellent organizational skills
- Analyze testing reports from external laboratories
- Comprehensive knowledge and troubleshooting in pharmaceutical softwares (Fillware, PK Compounding etc.)
- Barista Starbucks Coffee

OCT 2012 - OCT 2016

- Efficiently worked with team to execute routine tasks in a fast-paced environment, while solving daily conflicts or complaints by customers
- Demonstrate excellent customer service and communication skills to meet daily and weekly sales goals

Other Experience

Youth Counselor

Children's Aid Society

JAN 2016 - JAN 2019

- Counselled and assessed client's behaviours change, improvement and limitation
- Provide weekly one-on-one solution focused support

Educational Training

Web Development Immersive Bootcamp Juno College of Technology June 2020 - September 2020

Web Development Course

Bachelor of Arts in Psychology with

Honours

Juno College of Technology November 2019 - January 2020

York University April 2015